OK, now back to the show.
好了 现在回到表演
-James, what are you doing?Dad said no playing ball in the castle. -I just wanna show you one more trick.
-詹姆斯 你在干什么 父亲说了不能在城堡里玩球  -我只是想再给你们表演一个把戏
-But, dad said...  -Don't worry
-但是 父亲说  -不要担心
It is easy as one, two, three...
很简单的 一 二 三
Oh no .
噢 不
-The window! -The picture!
-窗户  -图画
I...I didn't mean to break it.
我 我不是故意打碎它的
Oh, dad is not going to like this.
噢 父亲不会喜欢这个的
-What do we do? -We have to go tell him.
-我们要怎么办  -我们必须去告诉他
W..wait, you can't tell dad.
等一下 你们不能告诉父亲
-If he finds out I broke the castle rule, he'll never let me go to the circus.-Oh.
-如果他发现我打破了城堡的规矩 他不会再让我去马戏团的  -噢
It doesn't matter whether we tell him, he's going to see the window when he comes back.
我们告诉不告诉他根本不重要 他回来时会看到窗户的